change contact info in two ways
firstam client
portal visit sunlife.com doph and click
the sign in button on the upper right of
the website second click settings on the
left side bar of your dashboard then
select edit contact details fourth
update then save your new contact
numbers or email address another option
is VI mobile app downlo M Play Store or
app store first sign in to your sunli pH
mobile app then click on service request
app on the bottom menu and click
personal details third click the edit
button on your mobile International home
business number or email address then
update and save your new contact numbers
or email address
[Music]
or
announcement Sun
privilege Sun client tune in for more
info thank you